yellowbridge.com 2019-03-13

# YellowBridge Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it accessible from the footer of every page on this site.

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the YellowBridge website. On some pages, you can subscribe to the site and make requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages include name, e-mail address, and your personal preferences for certain features provided on our site.

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when subscribing only to fulfill our subscription services. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

## Use of Cookies

This site uses cookies to improve its performance and enhance your user experience. Cookies are small text files which a website may put on your device in order to store certain information and use it on a subsequent visit. By continuing to browse this site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies. Disabling our cookies will disable all features enabled by them. We have three categories of cookies:

  * We use first-party cookies to store your usage preferences and enable other convenience features, such as the ability to stay signed on even after you have left our site.
  * Our advertising partners use third-party cookies to serve ads that are more relevant to your interests.
  * We use Google Analytics to monitor the performance of our site. Google Analytics uses third-party cookies for this purpose.

## Online Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. As stated above, some of these ads may place third-party cookies on your computer in order to serve ads based on your prior visits to one or more sites. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our advertising partner, has a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](https://exponential.com/privacy) or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com.

Google, Inc and its subsidiaries (including DoubleClick), as our advertising partner, has a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data, including cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details about how Google uses such information, please review their [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites).

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13.

## How To Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about theis Privacy Policy, please send us an email at support@yellowbridge.com.
